Osvaldo Gioia

Argentina



os.gioia@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/osvaldogioia

Summary

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Able to handle any part of the process with

ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 8 years of related experience.

Experience

Full Stack Engineer

Grupo Fidelatam

Mar 2021 - Present (4 months +)

Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.

Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and enhancements.

Built, tested and deployed scalable, highly available and modular software products.

Worked on loyalty enginnering projects using NodeJS and React.

.NET Developer

Recursiva

Nov 2020 - Mar 2021 (5 months)

Maintained existing applications and designed and delivered new applications.

Wrote code on platform using .NET Framework and Oracle.

Full Stack Developer

Do Until Plus

Oct 2014 - Dec 2020 (6 years 3 months)

Took initial concepts and developed project plans.

Wrote code on differents platform using .NET Framework, MS SQL and NodeJS.

Program Analyst

Close-Up International

Aug 2013 - Nov 2020 (7 years 4 months)

Helped solve diverse program problems with in-depth analysis.

Analyzed program data to provide input for key decision making and strategic planning.

Collected, organized and modeled data using Progress Openedge.

Collaborated with other developers to identify and alleviate software errors and inefficiencies.

Software Engineer

Obra Social de Unión de Trabajadores Hoteleros y Gastronómicos de la República Argentina

Sep 2011 - Jan 2013 (1 year 5 months)

Analyzed and designed relational databases using Progress Openedge.

Prepared detailed reports on updates to project specifications, progress, identified conflicts and team activities.

Education

*UTN Universidad Tecnológica Nacional

Tecnico Superior Programación, Programación 2009 - 2014

ITMaster Academy

Programador web 2018 - 2019

Licenses & Certifications

- Microservicios con un café LinkedIn
- in SCRUM con un café LinkedIn
- GitHub para programadores LinkedIn
- Lifelong Learning CertiProf Issued Aug 2020 - Expires Aug 2022
- n Node.js práctico: Sitio web LinkedIn
- Arquitecturas de Software Universidad Tecnológica Nacional BA
- Experto Universitario en Hacking Ético (Ethical Hacking) Universidad Tecnológica Nacional BA

Skills

C# • Python • JavaScript • Scrum • Red privada virtual (VPN) • Desarrollo del front-end • Integración continua · Desarrollo de aplicaciones · Software Design · XML